(កណ្តុរ)
(រឿងល្ខោននេះគឺជាការប្រឌិតសុទ្ធសាធហើយមិនត្រូវបានផ្សារភ្ជាប់ជាមួយនឹង ... )
(មនុស្សជាក់ស្តែងអង្គការទីតាំងឬឧប្បត្តិហេតុ។ )
(ការថតឯកសារគឺអនុលោមតាមគោលការណ៍ណែនាំនៃគម្រប -១១ ... )
(និងការផ្តល់ប្រឹក្សាត្រូវបានផ្តល់សម្រាប់អ្នកសំដែងកុមារ។ )
(CGI ត្រូវបានប្រើនៅក្នុងឈុតភាគច្រើនដែលរួមបញ្ចូលទាំងសត្វ។ )
តើអ្នកនៅទីនេះយ៉ាងដូចម្តេច?
មិនយូរប៉ុន្មានដានីយ៉ែលលីបានធ្វើឃាតកម្ម។
នេះជាគោលដៅបន្ទាប់របស់អ្នក។
ពិចារណាមនុស្សនេះជាមំសាសីលំដាប់កំពូល។
នេះគឺជាអាស័យដ្ឋានដែលគាត់បានអោយខ្ញុំ។
អ្នកប្រាកដជាមានការចងចាំល្អ។
អ្នកនឹងមានហ្សែនរបស់សត្វមំសាសីនិងទេពកោសល្យ។
ដូច្នេះហេតុអ្វីបានជាអ្នកនៅទីនេះ?
ស៊ុងយ៉ូហាននិងខ្ញុំ។
តើយើងជាសត្វកណ្តុរមន្ទីរពិសោធន៍របស់អ្នកទេ?
ខ្ញុំគួរតែចាប់ផ្តើមដោយអរគុណអ្នក។
អរគុណដែលធំឡើងក្លាយជាឃាតករ
ជុងបារាម។
វាអាក្រក់ណាស់ដែលស៊ុងយ៉ូហានធ្វើឱ្យខ្ញុំខកចិត្ត។
លុះត្រាតែវិក័យប័ត្របញ្ឈប់ការមានផ្ទៃពោះ ...
ជាមួយនឹងទារកក្នុងផ្ទៃដែលផ្ទុកហ្សែនផ្នែកចិត្តសាស្រ្តត្រូវបានអនុម័ត ...
Actually,
I thought it being dismissed gave me an opportunity.
The assembly would've never agreed to it anyway.
In order for the bill to pass, I knew I needed a long-term plan.
A long-term plan?
That's why you went to Daniel.
I asked for the list of mothers who were pregnant...
with babies carrying the psychopath gene.
Daniel was in shock after finding out...
that Han Seo Joon had killed his sister,
so he was easy to convince.
Is this the right course of action?
I can't be certain either.
However, we can't reach Utopia without going through a war...
or fighting off crimes.
It's ours to build.
Think about Jennifer's death.
Let's make sure that no one dies like she did.
Once we grew up to be psychopathic killers,
you were to use that as evidence to pass the bill.
You did so by forming a black ops unit...
នៅក្នុងសេវាស៊ើបការណ៍សម្ងាត់ជាតិ។
ត្រឹមត្រូវហើយ។
យើងសង្កេតឃើញម្តាយនិងទារកក្នុងផ្ទៃអំឡុងពេលមានផ្ទៃពោះ។
ដើម្បីធ្វើឱ្យប្រាកដថាកុមារត្រូវបាននាំយកទៅតាមលក្ខខណ្ឌ។
ផ្តល់កំណើតឱ្យកូនរបស់អ្នក។
នៅពេលដែលក្មេងប្រុសទាំងពីរកើតមក
ភ្នាក់ងារត្រូវបានគេដាក់ឱ្យសង្កេតមើលសកម្មភាពរបស់ពួកគេ។
ពួកគេនឹងបញ្ជូនរបាយការណ៍របស់ពួកគេហើយអ្នកជំនាញធ្វើការវិភាគ ...
អ្វីដែលត្រូវបានគេសង្កេតឃើញ។
នោះហើយជាមូលហេតុដែលអ្នកបញ្ជាទិញសុងសូហូ ...
ដើម្បីសំលាប់ម្តាយរបស់ខ្ញុំដែលបានព្យាយាមសំលាប់ខ្ញុំ ...
និងគ្រួសាររបស់ខ្ញុំដែលនៅសល់?
នោះគឺជាគ្រោះថ្នាក់។
វាបានបំផ្លាញសុងសូហូទាំងស្រុង។
ប៉ុន្តែគាត់គ្មានជំរើសទេ។
បើគ្មានអ្នកទេការពិសោធន៍នឹងត្រូវបានបញ្ចប់។
តើអ្នកអាចទាញយកផលប្រយោជន៍ពីសមាជិកគ្រួសារជនរងគ្រោះយ៉ាងដូចម្តេច?
តើមនុស្សមានលក្ខណៈដូចម្ដេច?
យើងគ្រាន់តែឱ្យគាត់ដឹងដូច្នេះយើងអាចសុបិន្តពិភពតែមួយ។
ពិភពលោកដែលគ្មានជនរងគ្រោះគ្មានសមាជិកគ្រួសារដែលបាត់បង់
និងគ្មានបទឧក្រិដ្ឋ។
ហេតុអ្វីបានជាអ្នកមិនចូលរួម
នៅពេលដែលខ្ញុំចាប់ផ្តើមសម្លាប់ឃាតករចិត្តសាស្រ្តផ្សេងទៀត?
វាជាការពិតដែលថាសកម្មភាពរបស់អ្នកបានធ្វើឱ្យខ្ញុំប្រុងប្រយ័ត្ន។
ប៉ុន្តែការមើលឃើញជាសាធារណៈថាអ្នកជាវីរៈបុរសបានផ្លាស់ប្តូរគំនិតខ្ញុំ។
នៅពេលដែលសាធារណជនដែលបានឃើញអ្នកជាអ្នកធ្វើសង្គ្រាម។
ស្វែងយល់ពីអ្នក
ពួកគេនឹងត្រូវខ្ទេចខ្ទី។
ហើយការអនុម័តវិក្កយបត្រនឹងកាន់តែងាយស្រួល។
អ្នកបានឆ្លៀតយកប្រយោជន៍ពីក្រុមគ្រួសារជនរងគ្រោះ ...
និងបានសម្លាប់ប្រជាជនស្លូតត្រង់។
អ្នកគឺជាសត្វចម្លែកដូចខ្ញុំដែរចយយ៉ុងស៊ីន។
ខ្ញុំពិតជាអ្នកវិទ្យាសាស្ត្រ។ អ្នកជំនាញខាងពន្ធុវិទ្យាត្រូវពិតប្រាកដ។
មានតែវិទ្យាសាស្ត្រទេដែលអាចដោះស្រាយឧក្រិដ្ឋកម្មនៃពិភពលោកនេះ។
ការបញ្ឈប់ឃាតករសក្តានុពលមុនពេលពួកគេកើត ...
ដូច្នេះយើងអាចរស់នៅក្នុង Utopia គ្មានឃាតកម្មការប្រយុទ្ធនិងសង្គ្រាម ...
គឺជាគោលដៅចុងក្រោយរបស់ខ្ញុំ។
នៅលើពិភពលោកខ្ញុំសុបិនចង់
ឃាតករចិត្តសាស្ត្រដូចជាអ្នកមិនគួរមានទេ។
អ្នកនឹងមិនត្រូវបាននាំឱ្យមានរយៈពេល។
ទៅ​ពេល​ខាង​មុខ។ សម្លាប់​ខ្ញុំ។
ស្លាប់យ៉ាងសាហាវនៅក្នុងដៃរបស់អ្នក…
នឹងធ្វើឱ្យយើងឈានមួយជំហានខិតទៅជិតពិភពសុបិន្តរបស់ខ្ញុំ។
សង្គមកាន់តែវិវត្តទៅជាហ្សែនផ្នែកចិត្តសាស្ត្រ ...
រីករាលដាលពាសពេញពិភពលោកដូចជាជម្ងឺ។
ថ្ងៃមួយ
អ្នកដែលមានហ្សែនផ្នែកចិត្តសាស្រ្តនឹងបំផ្លាញយើងជាមនុស្សសាមញ្ញ។
មុនពេលរឿងនោះកើតឡើង
ហ្សែនផ្នែកចិត្តសាស្រ្តត្រូវតែលុបបំបាត់ចោល។
សម្លាប់​ខ្ញុំ។ សម្លាប់​ខ្ញុំ!
តើកន្លែងនេះជាអ្វី?
តើផ្ទះនេះជាអ្នកណា?
តើមានអ្វីនៅលើផែនដី?
តើនេះជាផ្ទះសំណាក់នៅរដូវក្តៅមែនទេ?
សុងសូហូ!
(ដែនដីអូរហ្សីដែលជាតំបន់អ៊ូបផូបគ្មានទីពឹង)
អ្នកស៊ើបអង្កេតលី?
តើមានអ្វីនៅលើផែនដី?
កុំព្យូទ័រយួរដៃ។
គាត់បានស្លាប់ដោយសារតែកុំព្យូទ័រយួរដៃនោះ។
នេះគឺជាកន្លែងដែលអ្នកបោកប្រាស់បានសម្លាប់អ្នកស៊ើបអង្កេតស៊ីន។
សម្លាប់​ខ្ញុំ។ សម្លាប់ខ្ញុំរួចហើយ!
ដើម្បីសង្គ្រោះជីវិតខ្ញុំ
អ្នកលុតជង្គង់នៅមុខហានស៊ីអូជុន។
ប៉ុន្តែការវះកាត់នោះ ...
ផ្តល់ឱ្យខ្ញុំនូវអារម្មណ៍ដែលមាននរណាម្នាក់ដូចខ្ញុំមិនគួរមានអារម្មណ៍។
មន្ទីរពិសោធន៍កណ្តុររបស់អ្នក ...
មិនអាចសម្លាប់ទៀតទេ។
ទេ
សម្លាប់​ខ្ញុំ។ សម្លាប់ខ្ញុំឥឡូវនេះ។
ប្រញាប់ឡើងសម្លាប់ខ្ញុំទៅ!
តាមវិធីនេះមនុស្សនឹងទៅរស់នៅក្នុងពិភពលោកដែលមានសុវត្ថិភាពនិងសន្តិភាព!
សម្លាប់​ខ្ញុំ! ប្រញាប់ឡើងសម្លាប់ខ្ញុំទៅ!
អ្នក ...
គឺគួរអោយអាណិតណាស់។
ជុងបារាមអ្នកលេងសើចនោះ។
អ្នកមានសារជាសំលេងមួយ។
អ្នកស៊ើបអង្កេតកូខ្ញុំនឹងសម្លាប់បុរសដែលសម្លាប់យាយខ្ញុំ។
ខ្ញុំក៏នឹងសងសឹកជំនួសបងប្រុសរបស់អ្នកដែរ។
ដុសខាត់វា។ បងប៊ីយី!
លោកស្រី គីម?
តើ​អ្នក​កំពុង​ធ្វើអ្វី​នៅ​ទីនេះ?
បារាម! បារ៉េមនៅទីណា?
ត្រជាក់ចិត្ត។ គាត់បានធ្វើវាដើម្បីការពារអ្នកឱ្យមានសុវត្ថិភាព។
ដើម្បីឱ្យខ្ញុំមានសុវត្ថិភាព?
ឆាប់អ្នកនឹងរកឃើញការពិត។
អូហូងយីនឹងត្រូវគេយកទៅហើយរកឃើញថាជាសាកសពមែនទេ?
ឬនាងនឹងត្រូវបោះបង់ចោលដោយសុវត្ថិភាពនៅគោលដៅរបស់នាង?
ខ្ញុំគិតថាពួកគេអាចនឹងចាប់ចំណាប់ខ្មាំងរបស់នាង។
ត្រូវប្រាកដថានាងមិនដែលចាកចេញពីកន្លែងនេះរហូតដល់ខ្ញុំបានធ្វើ។
សូមថែរក្សានៅសល់។
បារាម។
អ្នក ...
លែងជាមនុស្សដែលអ្នកធ្លាប់ជា
គ្រាន់តែឃើញថាអ្នកមិនបានសំលាប់ Choi Young Shin ។
នោះនៅតែមិនផ្លាស់ប្តូរអ្វីទាំងអស់។
បារាម! បារាម!
តើអ្នកអាចតាមដានទូរស័ព្ទដៃរបស់ Bong Yi បានទេ?
ឆ្មាមួយ ...
បារាម, ដុកទ័រដុន។
សួស្តី?
ដុំប្លាស្ទិកនោះមកពីរបាំងពពែមេន។
យើងបានរកឃើញឌីអិនអេរបស់គីមហានកឃីនៅលើវា។
វាគឺបារាម។
គាត់ជាមនុស្សឆ្កួតដែលបានសម្លាប់បងប្អូនខ្ញុំ។
- មន្រ្តីជុង? - អ្នកស៊ើបអង្កេត Ko Moo Chi!
អ្នកស៊ើបអង្កេត Ko ។
អ្នកស៊ើបអង្កេត។
តើធ្វើដូចម្តេចអំពីភេសជ្ជៈមួយ?
មន្រ្តីជុងខ្ញុំបាន heard ...
អ្នកតែងតែល្អចំពោះបងប្រុសរបស់ខ្ញុំ។
ខ្ញុំចង់ក្លាយជាប្រភេទបងប្រុសដែល Moo Won ធ្លាប់នៅជាមួយខ្ញុំ។
ប៊ងយី។
អ្នកឆ្កួតគួរឱ្យស្អប់ខ្ពើម។
តើ​វា​សប្បាយ​ទេ?
តើអ្នករីករាយនឹងខ្លួនអ្នកទេ?
អ្នកត្រូវតែបានរកឃើញថាវាគួរឱ្យចង់សើចណាស់នៅជុំវិញខ្ញុំ។
បើគ្មានតម្រុយតិចតួចទេ
ខ្ញុំបានបញ្ចប់ការដួលសម្រាប់បុរសដែលបានសម្លាប់យាយខ្ញុំ។
តើអ្នកសប្បាយទេ?
លោកយាយតើអ្នកកំពុងមើលទេ?
សូមផ្តល់កម្លាំងឱ្យខ្ញុំ។
ផ្តល់ឱ្យខ្ញុំនូវភាពក្លាហាន។
ភ្នែកសម្រាប់ភ្នែក, ធ្មេញសម្រាប់ធ្មេញ។
សម្រង់សំណព្វរបស់អ្នក។
ខ្ញុំនឹងធ្វើអ្វីដែលអ្នកបានធ្វើចំពោះយាយរបស់ខ្ញុំ។
ខ្ញុំនឹងសម្លាប់អ្នក។
ទៅមុខហើយសម្លាប់ខ្ញុំផង។
សម្លាប់ខ្ញុំដូចអ្នកសម្លាប់យាយខ្ញុំ!
ទេបង Bong Yi ។ ខ្ញុំមិនអាចធ្វើឱ្យអ្នកក្លាយជាឃាតករបានទេ។
យាយរបស់ខ្ញុំយកចិត្តទុកដាក់ចំពោះអ្នកខ្លាំងណាស់។
តើអ្នកអាចធ្វើយ៉ាងម៉េចចំពោះនាង?
របៀប ...
ប៊ងយី។
បងប៊ីយីខ្ញុំសុំទោស។
យាយ​របស់​ខ្ញុំ...
ខ្ញុំសុំទោសគ្រប់យ៉ាង។
ខ្ញុំ ...
ខ្ញុំនឹងចូលខ្លួនឯង។
សូមឱ្យខ្ញុំបង្វែរខ្លួនខ្ញុំចូល។
បងប៊ីយីខ្ញុំសុំទោស។
Bong ... Bong យី។
អ្នក!
បាទ​វា​គឺ​ត្រឹមត្រូវ។ ខ្ញុំបានសម្លាប់ Kang Duk Soo ។
គឺដោយសារតែអ្នក។
ខ្ញុំបានសម្លាប់គាត់ព្រោះខ្ញុំគិតថាអ្នកនឹងមានគ្រោះថ្នាក់។
ខ្ញុំ ...
ឈឺ។
ប៉ុន្តែខ្ញុំគិតថាខ្ញុំអាចនឹងប្រសើរឡើង។
ខ្ញុំបានឃើញក្តីសង្ឃឹមថ្ងៃនេះ។
អ្នកមិន ...
សូម្បីតែសមនឹងស្លាប់ដូចនេះ។
បង្វែរខ្លួនអ្នកចូល។
បង្វែរខ្លួនអ្នកហើយរស់នៅពេញមួយជីវិតដោយវេទនា។
ខ្ញុំសង្ឃឹមថាកំហុសរបស់អ្នកនឹងស៊ីអ្នក។
ខ្ញុំសង្ឃឹមថាអ្នករស់នៅដោយប្រាថ្នាចង់អោយអ្នកស្លាប់។
នោះហើយជារបៀបដែលខ្ញុំចង់អោយអ្នកបង់ថ្លៃអំពើបាបរបស់អ្នក។
Bong Yi ...
គឺ​អ្នក។
អ្នកបានសម្លាប់បងប្អូនរបស់ខ្ញុំ។
អ្នកស៊ើបអង្កេត Ko ។
សូម ...
ចាប់ខ្ញុំ។
ខ្ញុំនឹងធ្វើអ្វីដែលអ្នកចង់ធ្វើ។
ខ្ញុំសូមធ្វើវា។
កុំសាកល្បងសំរាមនៅលើខ្ញុំអ្នកកខ្វក់!
សូមមេត្តាកុំបំផ្លាញជីវិតអ្នកឡើយ។
ខ្ញុំនឹង ...
ខ្ញុំ​នឹង​ធ្វើ​វា។
កុំនិយាយកុហកខ្ញុំ, អ្នកកខ្វក់។
ថ្ងៃទីបី។ លក្ខខណ្ឌល្អណាស់។
សកម្មណាស់។ គ្មានបញ្ហាត្រូវបានអង្កេតឃើញទេ។
ថ្ងៃទី ១១. ផ្លាស់ទីយឺត ៗ ។
ចលនាយឺតនិងកម្រិតសកម្មភាពទាប។
ថ្ងៃទី ២១. លក្ខខណ្ឌអាក្រក់ណាស់។
កម្រមានចលនាណាមួយ។
ថ្ងៃទី ៣០. មរណភាព។
(កណ្តុរ)
(ភាគបញ្ចប់)
(ជុងបារាមប្រែខ្លួនជាអ្នកនិយាយថា“ ខ្ញុំជាឃាតករស៊ែរ”) ។
ណឺដ។
ទេ!
(ជុងបារាមប្រែខ្លួនជាអ្នកនិយាយថា“ ខ្ញុំជាឃាតករស៊ែរ”) ។
- អ្នកសម្លាប់! - បិសាច!
- ឱ្យគាត់ឆ្លងកាត់។ - ឃាតករនោះ!
នាំគាត់មកវិញ!
នាំកូនប្រុសខ្ញុំមកវិញ! នាំកូនប្រុសខ្ញុំមកវិញ!
នាំកូនប្រុសខ្ញុំមកវិញ!
តើអ្នកអាចធ្វើដូច្នេះដោយរបៀបណា?
- បិសាចអ្នក! - ថយចេញ។
- ឈរត្រឡប់មកវិញ។ - បិសាចអ្នក!
រក្សាការសន្យារបស់អ្នក។
រក្សាការសន្យារបស់អ្នកចំពោះម៉ូជី។
តោះ​ចាប់ផ្ដើម។ ចាប់ផ្តើមប្រើថ្នាំសន្លប់។
លើកក្បាលរបស់អ្នក។
ខ្ញុំនឹងចាប់ផ្តើមស្រក់ឥឡូវនេះ។
ខ្ញុំ​ខ្លាច។
ខ្ញុំ​អត់​សប្បាយចិត្ត។
ពន្លឺព្រះអាទិត្យដែលចាក់នៅចន្លោះស្លឹកធ្វើឱ្យខ្ញុំខកចិត្ត។
- រង់ចាំ។ - វិកលចរិត ...
មិនអាចមានអារម្មណ៍អ្វីទាំងអស់។
ប្រសិនបើគាត់មិនមែនជាឃាតករ
ហេតុអ្វីបានជារូបភាពនៃរាងកាយរបស់ Byun Soon Young នៅទីនេះ?
គាត់បានលាក់បាំងហានកឃីនៅទីនេះហើយនាំគាត់ទៅមន្ទីរពេទ្យដែលគេបោះបង់ចោល។
("ដានហាន់ឃីកត្រូវបានរក្សាទុកនៅក្នុងមន្ទីរពេទ្យដែលគេបោះបង់ចោលត្រូវបានរកឃើញ")
ប្រាកដ។ ប្រសិនបើមានអ្វីនៅទីនេះប៉ូលីសនឹងរកឃើញ។
លោកស្រី ចុយ?
វេជ្ជបណ្ឌិតលី។
តើវាជាបារាមមែនទេ?
ខ្ញុំនឹងស្លាប់ទៅហើយបើវាមិនមែនសំរាប់យ៉ូហាន។
ខ្ញុំមិនដឹងទេ ...
និងបានប្រាប់លោក Choi Young Shin ...
តើអ្នកទំនេរនៅយប់ថ្ងៃស្អែកទេ?
ខ្ញុំនឹងប្រាប់អ្នកទាំងអស់គ្នានូវថ្ងៃស្អែក។
ខ្ញុំបានសម្លាប់អ្នក។
វាជាកំហុសរបស់ខ្ញុំ។
ហេតុអ្វីបានជាប៉ូលីសមិនរកវាឃើញ?
មានផ្លូវចូលលូ។
ខ្ញុំបានលាក់ខ្លួននៅទីនោះនៅពេលដែលប៉ូលីសបានឆ្មក់ចូល។
ខ្ញុំ​ឃើញ។
ខ្ញុំនឹងមើលថែអ្នករហូតដល់អ្នកបានជាសះស្បើយ។
សូមអរគុណ។
ខ្ញុំនឹងធ្វើអ្វីក៏ដោយដើម្បីលុបឈ្មោះយូហាន។
ទេ
នោះមិនគ្រប់គ្រាន់ទេ។
បារាមបាត់បង់ការចងចាំ។
គាត់គិតថាគាត់ជាមនុស្សចិត្តល្អ។
ប្រើគាត់មុនពេលសភាវគតិរបស់គាត់ភ្ញាក់
និងកម្ចាត់ scumbags ដែលសមនឹងស្លាប់។
ហើយប្រសិនបើឆយយ៉ាំងស៊ីប្រាប់ពិភពលោកថាគាត់ជានរណា?
យើងនឹងវាយនាងហើយប្រាប់ពិភពលោកថាបារាមគឺជានរណា ...
និងអំពើគួរស្អប់ខ្ពើមដែលនាងបានធ្វើ។
ហានសៅជុនបានប្រើខ្ញុំដើម្បីទាក់ទាញជនរងគ្រោះរបស់គាត់ដែលគាត់បានសម្លាប់។
ខ្ញុំបានឃើញពីការជិតស្និទ្ធ ...
អ្វីដែលគាត់គឺជាសត្វចម្លែក។
មនុស្សដូចនោះមិនអាចផ្លាស់ប្តូរបានទេ។
សូមអោយអ្នកទាំងអស់គ្នាដកខ្លួនចេញ ...
ដូចជាបារេម។
សូមប្រាកដថាគ្មាននរណាម្នាក់បញ្ចប់ដូចបងស្រីរបស់អ្នកទេ ...
ឬយូហានម្តងទៀត។
បន្ទាប់មកខ្ញុំនឹងត្រូវការឧបករណ៍មន្ទីរពិសោធន៍។
(ជុងបារាមប្រែខ្លួនជាអ្នកនិយាយថា“ ខ្ញុំជាឃាតករស៊ែរ”) ។
សម្លាប់ឃាតករនោះ!
តោះ​ទៅ។ តោះ​ទៅ!
ខ្ញុំត្រូវតែសំលាប់កខ្វក់នោះ។ តោះ​ទៅ!
ខ្ញុំត្រូវតែសម្លាប់គាត់!
- ខ្ញុំត្រូវតែសំលាប់គាត់។ - ត្រជាក់ចិត្ត។
អ្នកដឹងពីរបៀបដែលគាត់បានសម្លាប់បងប្អូនរបស់ខ្ញុំ។
អេ​លោក! ចេញពីទីនេះ។
តោះ​ទៅ! ហេ។
ហេ!
(ភ្នាក់ងារប៉ូលីសម៉មមីន)
អ្នកត្រូវប្រាប់យើងពីមូលហេតុដែលអ្នកត្រូវបានចងភ្ជាប់នៅក្នុងផ្ទះនោះ។
តើមានអ្វីកើតឡើង ...
នៅសួនកម្សាន្តមួយឆ្នាំមុន?
និយាយអ្វីមួយ។ តើអ្នកចង់បានមេធាវីទេ?
- ស្អី? - ម្តាយរបស់ស៊ុងយូហាន ...
កំពុងតែសុំមើលបារាម។
អ្វី? គ្មានផ្លូវទេ។ នាងនឹងព្យាយាមសម្លាប់គាត់។
គ្មានអ្វីនឹងកើតឡើងទេ។ ឱ្យនាងជួបគាត់។
ខ្ញុំសង្ស័យថានាងនឹងសម្លាប់កូនប្រុសខ្លួនឯង។
កូនប្រុស​របស់​នាង?
ម៉ាក់មានក្មេងប្រុសចំលែកម្នាក់នៅក្នុងថ្នាក់ខ្ញុំ។
គាត់បានទន្សាយទន្សាយ។
ខ្ញុំត្រូវប្រាកដថាដូច្នេះខ្ញុំបានទៅផ្ទះរបស់អ្នក។
មើលមួយគឺអ្វីដែលខ្ញុំត្រូវការ។
តើ​អ្នក​មិន​អី​ទេ​ឬ?
ទៅផ្ទះ។ រត់ទៅផ្ទះឥឡូវនេះ!
ម៉ាក់!
នេះ។
ស្លាប់។ បិសាចដូចជាអ្នកត្រូវការស្លាប់។
អ្នកបិសាច។
ខ្ញុំមិនគួរផ្តល់កំណើតឱ្យអ្នកទេ។
ខ្ញុំមិនគួរផ្តល់កំណើតឱ្យអ្នក។
នោះមិនមែនជាសុបិនទេ។
អ្នកគួរតែសម្លាប់ខ្ញុំពេលនោះ។
ហេតុអ្វីបានជាអ្នកមិនធ្វើដូច្នេះ?
ហេតុអ្វី?
ហេតុនេះ​ហើយ...
យើងប្តូរកូនរបស់យើង។
ខ្ញុំជេមីន?
ប៉ុន្តែគាត់មិនបាននិយាយអ្វីទាំងអស់។
គាត់ប្រហែលជាភ័យខ្លាចខ្លាំងពេក។
ខ្ញុំបានឃើញគាត់។
គាត់បានព្យាយាមកប់បងប្រុសរបស់គាត់។
អ្នកចាំទេ ...
ការសន្យារបស់យើងមែនទេ?
ប្រសិនបើ Jae Hoon មិនត្រូវបានបញ្ឈប់
គាត់នឹងបញ្ចប់ការសម្លាប់ប្អូនប្រុសរបស់គាត់។
ដូច្នេះ​សូម,
សម្រាប់ជាប្រយោជន៍របស់ Jae Hoon ។
អ្នកប្រហែលជាគិតហើយ ...
ដែលខ្ញុំបានសម្លាប់គ្រួសាររបស់ខ្ញុំ។
ត្រូវហើយ។
ខ្ញុំបានស្វែងរកអ្នកចេញ ...
សម្លាប់អ្នកដោយខ្លួនឯង
ប៉ុន្តែម្តាយមីងរបស់អ្នកបាននាំអ្នកទៅហើយ។
ខ្ញុំបានរកអ្នកនៅគ្រប់ទីកន្លែង
ប៉ុន្តែគ្មានប្រយោជន៍ទេ។
នៅពេលខ្ញុំដឹងថាលេខអត្តសញ្ញាណប័ណ្ណរបស់អ្នកបានផុតកំណត់
ខ្ញុំ​បាន​បួងសួង...
ពីព្រោះអ្នកលែងរស់។
ហើយដូច្នេះខ្ញុំភ្លេចអ្នកបន្តិចម្តង ៗ ។
ស្ត្រីម្នាក់មានអាយុជាង ៧០ ឆ្នាំត្រូវបានគេរកឃើញនៅយប់នេះ…
ចាក់ដល់ស្លាប់ដោយរបួសជាច្រើនកន្លែង…
នៅក្នុងផ្ទះទំនេរមួយនៅក្នុងភូមិហ្គូដុងស្រុកអភិវឌ្ឍន៍។
ប៉ូលីសជឿជាក់ថានេះត្រូវបានប្រព្រឹត្តដោយ ...
បិសាចដូចជាអ្នកត្រូវការស្លាប់។
អ្នកបិសាច។
ខ្ញុំមិនគួរផ្តល់កំណើតឱ្យអ្នកទេ។
ខ្ញុំមិនគួរផ្តល់កំណើតឱ្យអ្នក។
ដូច្នេះមានជនរងគ្រោះចំនួន ៦ នាក់ត្រូវបានសម្លាប់ដោយឃាតករសៀរៀល។
ខ្ញុំដឹងថាវាជាអ្នក។
នោះត្រូវតែឈឺចាប់។
តើគាត់អាចធ្វើយ៉ាងម៉េចចំពោះមុខរបស់ក្មេង?
ហេតុអ្វីបានជាអ្នករៀបការជាមួយខ្ញុំ?
ហេតុអ្វីបានជាអ្នករៀបការជាមួយខ្ញុំពេលដែលអ្នកមិនស្រឡាញ់ខ្ញុំ?
ខ្ញុំគិតថាអ្នកអាចហៅវាបាន ...
ឆន្ទៈរបស់ខ្ញុំដើម្បីបង្កើតឡើងវិញ។
ខ្ញុំត្រូវការកូនចៅ។
អាហានសៅជូន័រ។
វារំmeកខ្ញុំពីខ្លួនខ្ញុំនិងហានសៅជុន។
ត្រឡប់មកវិញពេលខ្ញុំស្រលាញ់គាត់
ត្រូវបានគេ clueless ដូចដែលគាត់ជា។
តើ​អ្នក​មិន​អី​ទេ​ឬ?
ហេតុអ្វីបានជាអ្នកមិនចាត់វិធានការ?
មុនពេលដែលខ្ញុំអាចធ្វើបាន
យ៉ូហានបានរកឃើញអ្នកមុន។
យូហាន ...
បន្ទាប់ពីបញ្ជូនគាត់ទៅ
ខ្ញុំបានទៅបន្ទប់មន្ទីរពេទ្យរបស់អ្នក ...
ដើម្បីបញ្ចប់វាម្តងនិងសម្រាប់ទាំងអស់។
តើបក្សីនៅឯណា?
តើខ្ញុំនៅឯណា?
បារាម។ បារាម!
(ការឈប់សំរាកដាច់ខាត)
អ្នក​ជា​នរណា?
មន្រ្តីជុងធ្វើដំណើរទៅផ្ទះនៅថ្ងៃនេះបន្ទាប់ពីបានជាសះស្បើយពីការវះកាត់ចំនួន ៣ ។
នេះបើតាមការបញ្ជាក់ពីក្រុមគ្រូពេទ្យរបស់គាត់នៅមន្ទីរពេទ្យសាកលវិទ្យាល័យមូម៉ាជី។
គាត់បានជាសះស្បើយពេញលេញ។
ទោះយ៉ាងណាក៏ដោយគាត់កំពុងទទួលរងពីការភ្លេចភ្លាំងតាមមូលដ្ឋាន ...
ដោយសារតែការភ្ញាក់ផ្អើលនៃការវាយប្រហារ។
ខ្ញុំបានទៅផ្ទះដែលអ្នកបានរើទៅ
ហើយអ្នកហាក់ដូចជា ...
ដូចជាមនុស្សដែលមានចិត្តល្អ។
ខ្ញុំបានឃ្លាំមើលអ្នកតាំងពីថ្ងៃនោះតទៅ ...
ហើយសកម្មភាពរបស់អ្នកធ្វើអោយខ្ញុំមានសង្ឃឹម។
ថាប្រហែលជា ... ប្រហែលជា ...
អ្នកអាចផ្លាស់ប្តូរ។
វាជាមូលហេតុដែល ...
នោះ​ហើយ​ជា​មូល​ហេតុ​ដែល...
ដល់​ខ្ញុំ,
ហានសៅជូនហើយអ្នកគឺម្នាក់ ...
និងដូចគ្នា។
ដល់ពេលដែលអ្នកត្រូវសាកសួរហើយ។
ខ្ញុំដឹងថារឿងនេះនឹងមិនផ្លាស់ប្តូរអ្វីទាំងអស់
ប៉ុន្តែខ្ញុំមិនបានព្យាយាមសម្លាប់ Jae Min នៅថ្ងៃនោះទេ។
ហើយគ្រួសារខ្ញុំ ...
មិនមែនខ្ញុំទេដែលបានសម្លាប់ពួកគេ។
ទេអ្នកក៏គួរចាប់ខ្ញុំដែរ។
ខ្ញុំបានសម្លាប់បុរសម្នាក់។
ខ្ញុំបានសម្លាប់បុរសស្លូតត្រង់ម្នាក់ដើម្បីជួយសង្រ្គោះសត្វចម្លែកនោះ។
- ប៉ុន្តែ ... - ចាប់ខ្ញុំ។
- អ្នកស៊ើបអង្កេត ... - ខ្ញុំបានសម្លាប់បុរសស្លូតត្រង់ម្នាក់!
- វា​គ្រប់គ្រាន់​ហើយ។ - បញ្ឈប់ការនេះ។
- ឈប់! - ចាប់គាត់។
ឆាប់​ឡើង។
យកគាត់។
ចេញទៅ។
នៅទីនោះ។
តើអ្នកបានបាញ់គាត់ទេ?
យូហានក្រីក្ររបស់ខ្ញុំ។ ក្មេងកំសត់…
យ៉ូហានខ្ញុំ ...
អ្នកមិនមែនជាមនុស្សដែលបានយកជីវិតរបស់គាត់,
ដូច្នេះមិនចាំបាច់មានអារម្មណ៍ថាមានកំហុសទេ។
ហានសៅជុនគឺជាអ្នកដែលបានសម្លាប់គាត់។
វាមិនមែនជាអ្នកទេ។
Han Seo Joon has a hideout there.
You should check for yourselves.
That's it. That's what caused...
Ba Reum to change.
Is it true? Is she telling the truth?
Whom?
Sung Ji Eun?
Is Jung Ba Reum your son?
Is that why you implanted Yo Han's brain into Ba Reum's...
even though he was still alive?
Yes, it's all true.
How was that even possible? You're a death-row convict.
There's nothing...
Choi Young Shin can't do in this country.
She even knelt before me.
She told me everyone in the country is praying for him to recover.
She asked me to save the national son.
Why do you think she knelt before you to save Ba Reum?
I thought you were a genius, but you're just as dumb as I am.
She completely used you and your son.
You just wait.
Your son will soon get disposed miserably.
Choi Young Shin.
That wench.
You want to know when I found out?
You monster.
I shouldn't have given birth to you.
- I shouldn't have... - I told myself it couldn't be true.
I tried not to believe it...
even though I was abused for being a murderer's son.
Yo Han, please bring me my beige coat.
That day, I saw a photo of you holding some other baby.
So I took a specimen of your DNA and Han Seo Joon's...
to request a DNA test.
You should've called before you came.
What is it, sweetheart?
You knew, didn't you?
Knew what?
That your son is a murderer.
How...
How could you do this?
Yo Han...
Yo Han.
Yo Han, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
Let go of me.
You're no different.
You're just the same as your husband and son.
I won't ever forgive your son for killing my family...
and for brutally killing my one and only friend, Joon Sung.
And I won't forgive you for staying quiet...
even though you knew everything.
I'm going to kill your son today.
I'll kill him myself. You just wait and see.
No! No, Yo Han! Don't!
He's... He's a monster.
- Get out of my way. - You'll die.
You'll die too!
I said get out of my way!
Yo Han!
I brought the receipts...
Ms. Sung! Ms. Sung, wake up!
I didn't have the courage to tell you the truth.
I was scared you might hate and resent me.
My poor son, Yo Han.
You probably think I'm a terrible person.
But I want to be...
by your side.
Is Professor Lee still pleading the Fifth?
Yes. I don't get why he won't say anything when he's also a victim.
We won't get an arrest warrant if he refuses to speak.
The Blue House is getting involved, so it won't be easy to arrest her.
The presidential election is coming up too,
so they'll try their best to keep it quiet.
Exactly. Even if we file for an arrest warrant,
they'll reject it right away.
We'll just have to wait...
and hope Professor Lee testifies against her.
Increase the volume.
Is that Choi Young Shin's lawyer doing an interview?
My client doesn't know how that laptop...
and victims' belongings ended up at her house.
I'm sure Jung Ba Reum left it there on purpose.
I knew he'd say that.
- What is this? - What was that?
- What is this? - "OZ"?
What's that?
Hey, look at this. If we're lucky,
the tables might turn.
We have breaking news.
A, who confessed to have been a member...
of a private organization in the NIS,
- asked for a press interview... - She announced that she will...
disclose the shocking truth regarding a secret...
that the chief secretary has been keeping from us for 26 years.
What if Choi Young Shin finds a way out after I turn myself in?
Don't worry. This will prevent her from doing that.
Hoon Suk's father is on his way to pick him up.
I'll do a press interview as soon as he gets on a plane.
My gosh, what's going on?
- I hope we get something. - Exactly.
- I know. - What's it about?
- I wonder what's going on. - I don't know.
- I guess it's something shocking. - Let's hear her out.
It's been 30 minutes. Why is she so late?
Excuse me. Detective Kang.
Captain!
The darn father killed my parents.
And that son killed my brother.
I'll kill you. I swear.
Detective, you need to find my aunt first.
There's no time. In order to clear Sung Yo Han's name...
Brain implant and lab rats?
It sounds like a science fiction story.
My client is very dumbfounded by all the rumors.
Sung Yo Han and Jung Ba Reum...
are both psychopaths and murderers. That's the fact.
My aunt has evidence that can prove everything.
Can you zoom in on this?
Track down Detective Lee's cell. I'll go check his place.
- Hey, Ki Hyuk. - His cell phone's turned off.
I can't track his location.
(Special Task Force HQ)
(Interrogation Room)
They already took action.
But it's weird.
What is?
Choi Young Shin's side.
They look grim.
Lee Min Soo's missing?
What do you mean?
Didn't you say he called and said he was bringing her?
Yes, he did. But we can't reach him anymore.
Find him right now.
I'll keep looking.
Where?
I have to do something.
Captain. I have to clear Sung Yo Han's name.
I have to.
She's still not here.
Let's go.
Forget it. Let's go.
How did you find me?
Please.
I already promised Ba Reum.
I'm going to hold a press conference with the evidence that I have.
Ba Reum went to turn himself in.
I have a favor to ask.
I'm going to change the item tomorrow unannounced.
I need your help.
I need ironclad security.
You're the only person I can trust right now.
These are the files that I've gathered so far.
Look through them and then decide.
I'll do it. Someone has to.
As you saw, we don't have the smoking gun.
But let's try to get an arrest warrant.
Excuse me.
Hello.
- The house across the way... - Choi Young Shin was arrested,
and the police have 48 hours to charge her.
Given this unprecedented event,
they are focusing all efforts on having her charged.
We have to request a warrant soon.
Moo Chi still hasn't found Min Soo?
No. I haven't heard from him.
If the police fail to charge her,
it'll be very difficult for them...
to find the people involved higher up.
Min Soo.
They found Lee Min Soo.
Yes. I'm leaving now.
Yes.
Did you find her?
We can't reach Moo Chi.
It's time for your interview with the profiler.
I'm Choi Hong Ju of "Sherlock Hong Ju".
"I'm the real Moojin Serial Killer."
"I'm a serial killer."
Jung Ba Reum's confession has shocked the nation.
Tell me about the first murder. Why did you kill him?
I had been searching for Song Soo Ho for years.
He killed my family.
That was my first murder.
When I killed him,
it awoke the murderer inside of me.
- After that... - Commissioner.
What's more shocking than Jung Ba Reum's murders...
is the fact that there was someone...
who knew of his crimes, covered them up,
and actually induced him to commit the murders.
Dr. Daniel Lee said...
Sung Yo Han and I were both born with the psychopath gene.
Choi Young Shin...
observed us to see whether or not we grew up...
to be...
psychopathic murderers.
I'll escort you out.
Wait. It hasn't been 48 hours yet.
Then request a warrant.
You can't request a warrant because you have no evidence.
All you have is that lunatic's word.
If you won't request a warrant, don't keep her in here.
She's a busy woman doing the nation's work.
Why the hurry?
We still have five minutes.
Any word from Moo Chi?
Choi Young Shin used the national government to run...
an illegal surveillance on two children and their families.
That was possible...
because she was powerful enough...
to order around high-ranking officials.
Captain Bok!
Yes, sir.
What are you doing? Step aside.
We still have a minute.
Darn you, Ho Nam. Let her out.
Okay, we'll request the warrant.
Yes, sir.
(Arrest Warrant Request)
- Hello? - It's been rejected.
What garbage. You didn't have time to even open the email.
He didn't even review it.
Thank you for your service.
The murderer Jung Ba Reum's statements...
and that of Choi Young Shin, chief secretary to the president,
are in direct conflict.
However, I learned that the warrant for the arrest...
of Woo Hyung Chul, the Rope Knot Serial Killer,
was suddenly rejected.
I asked for the reason.
I have nothing to say.
Two more women were killed since the warrant was rejected.
Don't you regret it?
Don't blame me.
Do you think I wanted to reject it?
The order came down from above.
I was demoted and sent here because I argued against it.
We got an order from above.
They used all these big words about the public...
being traumatized.
It's weird when you think about it.
We can't go public because the higher-ups...
tell us to keep quiet.
That's not me.
He's nothing like me.
- He looks exactly like you. - Quiet.
Why did you deny the arrest warrant?
Did you order that the arrest warrant be denied?
Woo Hyung Chul's arrest warrant was denied as expected.
The organization even staged his crime scenes...
to make it look like it was a copycat killer.
Why?
That is an absurd accusation. That's stretching it.
Even if she did deny Woo Hyung Chul's arrest warrant,
how does that mean she induced Jung Ba Reum to murder?
Are you saying she controlled him?
In 1995, when the nation was in an uproar...
about the Head Hunter murders,
legislators met to discuss...
legalizing fetuses with the psychopath gene.
- Hey! - If you have something to say...
- How could this happen? - I didn't say anything wrong.
When the bill was rejected, Choi Young Shin came to me...
and asked me for a list of fetuses with the psychopath gene.
And I obliged.
Jung Ba Reum, Sung Yo Han,
and the child who was born already with the psychopath gene,
Woo Hyung Chul.
I went to her and told her to stop.
But she said...
The more people Jung Ba Reum kills,
the more the people will be enraged.
You're crazy.
You need to stop this now.
He's out of control right now.
A little later.
The presidential election is coming up.
Wait until then.
I'll get that law passed.
I never received any such document.
Dr. Daniel Lee is making an unfounded claim.
Is Dr. Daniel Lee really making an unfounded claim?
Are Jung Ba Reum and Dr. Lee lying about all of this?
It's the truth. All of it.
They found her.
They did it.
They already took action.
Choi Young Shin's side.
They look grim.
I think they lost Detective Lee.
He was the kidnapper, but they lost him?
I'll keep looking.
There's a picture.
In Detective Lee's home.
It was with that OZ we chased in the motel.
That 6264 OZ?
Yes. It was a picture of him, some woman...
and Detective Lee.
If Detective Lee didn't take my aunt to Choi Young Shin,
there must be a reason.
Yu Jung was stalked for seven years...
and killed by a man disguised as a delivery man.
Do you know him too?
Min Soo.
Min Soo and Yu Jung were inseparable during high school.
I see.
Do you know where Yu Jung's ashes were spread?
Min Soo!
You jerk. Where's the child and his mom?
You jerk. Don't tell me...
Who's that man, Mommy?
Don't scold him.
He said he'd take us to the TV station.
I'm sorry.
She said it was to make a world...
where people didn't have to die like Yu Jung.
Shall we?
Mister, you startled me!
A show's airing today? Shouldn't this be a secret?
You know I trust you.
And I trust you too.
It's why I brought them here.
I can't trust the police at this moment.
After joining the NIS in 2005, I was first stationed...
with the black-ops team OZ formed by Choi Young Shin.
When Song Soo Ho murdered Jung Ba Reum's entire family,
I stepped in as Ba Reum's aunt.
Moo Chi and Ba Reum worked together one last time.
From that moment on, my mission was...
to observe and report Ba Reum's actions.
Well, this...
I do not know this woman.
Do you have evidence that backs your claims?
I assure you that this isn't true.
This contains all the evidence you need.
("Sherlock Hong Ju")
(Choi Young Shin)
(Choi Young Shin's private organization OZ)
(Photos of victims right after they were murdered by Jung Ba Reum)
I have never seen them before. These were all fabricated.
Has he still not made a move?
Text Song Soo Ho's address to Jung Ba Reum.
Sorry?
Song Soo Ho's address?
Let's bait him.
How many has Jung Ba Reum killed so far?
The vineyard victim makes five.
It's still not enough.
We'll wait until the presidential election.
- What was that? - Can you explain?
- Give us your explanation. - Any words?
Arrest Choi Young Shin!
- Sure. - Yes, sir.
I'm afraid there's more than evidence on you.
Please step out.
Get out of the car.
Come on.
I bought these as a gift for Detective Shin's baby,
but he never got around to tell me that it was a girl.
You have the right to remain silent and the right to an attorney.
Anything you say can and will...
Why didn't you come forward sooner?
There isn't a government office...
that is free from Choi Young Shin's reach.
I'm sure that's why Sung Yo Han...
sought out Jung Ba Reum himself.
Then, was Sung Yo Han truly innocent?
Or was he a heinous killer just like Jung Ba Reum?
The grateful one who gave me back...
the will to live.
I'm not telling you to forgive him.
But until he kneels and begs for your forgiveness,
you should stay alive.
I'm talking about Doctor Sung Yo Han.
I was at the brink of death and he carried me to the police.
That young boy was Sung Yo Han.
Choi Young Shin tried to have me killed,
but Dr. Sung saved me and nursed me back to health.
While putting together this episode, I came across...
a recorded video.
(Sung Yo Han, 1 year ago, a few hours before he died)
I'll look forward to what you have to tell me tonight.
Are you perhaps going to propose?
I made lunch for you, so enjoy and see you later.
(Sung Yo Han, 1 year ago, a few hours before he died)
Daniel Lee told me...
that psychopaths never put on an act when they're alone.
(There's no scripted outro, so say whatever you want.)
I'm also...
hugely involved in this case.
I suggested to Daniel Lee...
that we take advantage of Jung Ba Reum.
When he told me the truth about Jung Ba Reum,
instead of reporting him to the police,
I used him to kill psychopaths...
such as Kang Duk Soo.
Once this show ends, I'll pay for what I did...
and fully cooperate with the police's investigation.
Here she comes!
Were you directly involved in the killings?
How did you conspire with Daniel Lee?
Do you have anything to say?
- Go ahead. - Any words?
- I am a killer. - What?
26 years ago, I killed a person.
Excuse me.
My daddy...
Where's your dad?
Excuse me. Sir.
Sir. Sir?
Please, don't kill me.
No, please.
Help.
I've lived with the guilt all my life.
I truly apologize to Soo Jung's mother.
(Choi Hong Ju's Shocking Confession, Deeply Involved in Jung's Murders)
- Detective Kang. - Yes?
Let me arrest her.
It took you a long time to come home.
Dad, I'm sorry.
After what I did to Soo Jung,
I couldn't let myself be happy.
Let's go.
Dad, where's Mom? Isn't she coming with us?
She told us to go first and wait for her.
What was your motive?
The organization known as OZ has come out of the shadows.
Chief Presidential Secretary Choi Young Shin...
formed a black-ops team...
in the name of creating a crimeless world.
Civilians were under surveillance...
and murder was commissioned in the process.
The people are raising their voices...
for a thorough investigation...
into the private organization that was motivated by personal greed.
Candidate Shin Sung Min was elected president...
in the 20th presidential election.
I thank the people for placing...
their sacred votes with me.
My late son Sang...
would've loved this the most.
(Shin Sung Min Elected as 20th President)
26 years ago, I dismissed a certain bill...
that came to my attention.
But today, I announce that...
I will let the people vote whether or not...
we should legally abort fetuses with psychopath genes.
(Execute Jung Ba Reum, the murderer!)
(You're just like your father!)
(The only solution is to execute Jung Ba Reum!)
The infamous serial killer, Jung Ba Reum,
will be having his first trial today.
The trial hasn't even started yet, but you can already see...
many funeral wreaths in front of Moojin Police Agency...
that were presumably sent by the citizens.
The citizens have finished casting their votes...
regarding whether or not there should be a law...
to abort fetuses with psychopath genes.
Based on the vote count, the government passed the bill...
Execute Jung Ba Reum!
The prosecution requested Jung Ba Reum to be executed,
and his first hearing will be held today at 3pm.
People are more interested to find out...
how long of a sentence Jung Ba Reum will receive...
and on what grounds...
the judges will base that sentence on,
which is why many people have tuned in to watch the live hearing.
I sentence the defendant, Jung Ba Reum, to death.
The serial killer, Jung Ba Reum,
got sentenced to death on his first trial.
The court announced that he should be isolated forever...
considering the unimaginable pain he gave to the victims.
Jung Ba Reum, who was once known as the national son,
shocked the entire country by confessing he was the culprit...
behind the Moojin serial murders.
Serial killer, Jung Ba Reum, canceled his appeal,
and that means his execution has been finalized.
(6 months later)
(The right kind of correction leads to a bright future.)
(3H28 1124)
(Emergency convoy)
(Establish law and order)
He's here?
Yes, that's him.
There you go. He finally has that look in his eyes again.
Your food's here.
You're the only guy I failed to kill.
You remember how your friend, Kim Byung Tae, died, right?
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.
You just wait.
Guard! Guard!
(As long as you have a dream, you can always start over again.)
(Walk in one line.)
(Do not talk while walking.)
Did you threaten Kim Soo Chul?
Did you threaten to kill him?
That darn rat.
He already told you that?
You're a monster.
How...
Why did you volunteer to work here?
Don't tell me...
you missed me. Is that why?
Did you miss me?
Yes.
I volunteered because I wanted to ask you something.
How could you do that?
How could you do that to Chi Kook?
How could you kill Bong Yi's grandmother and Father Ko?
How could you do that to them? How?
What's so wrong about a lion killing a few rats?
What?
Don't you want to know why I didn't kill you?
Because you weren't even worth it, you punk.
You jerk.
Hey...
Emergency in cell 7. Emergency in cell 7.
- Run. - Emergency in cell 7.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
What a nice weather.
It's a pity I can't go outside to see some flowers.
I missed you, Dad.
Yes.
I recognized you as soon as I saw the look in your eyes.
That you were just as superior as me.
Do you have...
anything else you want to say...
to me?
When I found out you were my son,
I was extremely happy.
I was proud of you.
Don't forget that we have superior genes than normal humans.
Don't ever change again.
Keep that look in your eyes.
Don't worry.
We'll be able to get out of here.
Do you think...
that's for the best?
Of course.
I have everything planned.
Dong Koo, listen to me.
Dong Koo!
When the time comes, open Han Seo Joon's cell for me.
I...
I need to finish it.
Breaking news. The Head Hunter, Han Seo Joon, was decapitated.
I should do what you did...
and kill you in front of your kid.
Han Seo Joon, I'll kill you...
using the worst way possible.
Keep your promise.
Keep your promise to Moo Chi.
(Prison guard saw it himself. Han Seo Joon, was decapitated.)
What's wrong?
Please... Please kill me.
Please kill me already.
I went to visit Hyun Soo.
She says Ba Reum is dying soon.
What?
It's the after effect of the brain transplant.
The prison guard says he can't bear to even look at him.
The pain must be excruciating.
He said it felt like a mouse was gnawing at his brain.
That's too easy for him.
He needs to suffer much more pain. Much more.
You have something to say to him as well.
- Go see him before he dies... - No!
Why should I see that dirtbag?
- Sit. Sit down. - Ma'am.
Why did you drink so much?
Stop drinking. You'll kill yourself at this rate.
Ma'am.
I need to ask you something.
You said you forgave...
that psychopathic father and son.
How did you forgive them? Did you lose your mind?
I'm not trying to forgive them...
for their sake.
It's for me. I want to live.
I feel like I'll die otherwise.
When I heard what Father Ko said,
I felt his pain and fatigue...
from all those years.
And I felt my pain and fatigue too.
That's when I let it all go.
I told myself to forgive.
That my kids would want me to live.
That I'll show them I'm doing well.
And then, I slept for days...
and days.
When I woke up,
I wanted to live.
Then... I was able to see...
Soo Jung and Soo Ho.
Don't give me that garbage.
I can't forgive him.
Of course. I understand.
Those of us who are left behind...
must find our own ways to live.
What matters is...
that we must live.
I wish you'd be free from your pain...
at least a little bit...
and find your life.
That's what your bother wanted too.
You're a lucky guy.
I hear you're dying on your own. Darn it.
I need to chop off your head and kill you.
I came to watch.
I wanted to see how pathetic you looked.
Do you think I'll forgive you because you chopped off...
your dad's head?
Dream on.
I'm sorry.
And I was always...
thankful.
In order to have the ability to kill someone,
you should have emptiness in your eyes.
But your eyes are filled with emotions.
Anger, pain, regrets, sympathy,
and love.
Now I understand what he meant by eyes being filled with emotions.
Your child is in pain and agony too.
I know I have no right, but I have a favor to ask.
Please use my assets...
to help the victims' families.
Do you think that will wash away an ounce of your sins?
And finally...
Bong Yi...
I miss Bong Yi.
You shameless jerk.
Would you come if you were her?
Let's go.
I hear you're dying.
I came to watch because I heard you were dying.
It would be so unfair...
if you die that comfortably.
Scum like you should die...
with sticks stuck in your stomach,
burned alive,
with your lungs removed,
with your stomach filled with stones...
That's how...
What did you want to say?
Why did you call me all the way here?
I wanted to say...
I'm sorry.
I...
will never forgive you...
for as long as I live.
I'll curse you for the rest of my life.
That's what I came to say.
In my next life...
I'll be born as an ordinary human being.
Then...
If I do...
(Visiting Room)
They say...
I was born a monster.
Please don't let me...
become a monster.
Please.
The Almighty...
heard your prayers.
You're no longer...
a monster.
(3 years later)
- A pardon? - No way!
Breaking news. President Shin Sung Min...
granted former secretary Choi Young Shin a pardon...
despite the protest from the people.
The Blue House stressed how this pardon...
could lead to a great union of our society.
- A pardon? - No way!
- A pardon? - No way.
Mom!
Eun Chong, come over here.
- Have you been well? - Yes.
The pardoning of Choi Young Shin...
stirred up wrath among the people...
which has led to a significant drop in the president's approval rating.
Get your eggs.
Your eggs!
Oh Bong Yi, eggs!
Get up. You'll be late for class.
The sun is high up in the sky!
- Darn him. - Get up and get to class!
- Please enjoy. Thank you. - Thank you.
- You're causing a commotion. - Don't you know what time it is?
Do you know how many eggs I need to sell...
to put you through college?
I'm going to pay you back, you know.
Besides, I said I didn't want to go to college.
Working the show and taking classes. I'm not Superwoman, you know.
Mister, you know,
I've been offered a job as the main writer for a new show.
You wait and see.
Once I get that job,
I'll build the fairest and most just world ever...
- so that no one feels wronged... - Hold on a second.
Your tuition money plus interest.
That new job comes with a salary raise, right?
When did you become a loan shark?
Unbelievable.
(Fresh Eggs)
- What's this? - Don't.
That's for me.
You hate beans as much as you hate carrots.
She'll be out by now, right?
Who?
Do you take me for an idiot?
Go to her.
Say you're sorry...
- and in person... - Get your eggs.
- Be a man and... - Big in size.
Get your fresh eggs.
They use recordings for that these days.
Only a geezer would use a megaphone.
Hey, kid. Don't you know that retro is trending?
Drop me off at the market.
- Why? - I invited Ms. Choi's family...
over for dinner.
Dong Koo will be there too.
You can come if you want.
How can I go there...
after what I have done?
Japchae and pork, check.
What else...
I almost forgot.
I should get some fried chicken for the kids.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
It was me who didn't trust him.
It's on me.
We both wronged him in a way we shouldn't be forgiven.
Right.
I'll atone for that until the day I die.
Same here.
I want you to be happy.
You too.
I'll try to be for Eun Chong's sake.
See you around then.
Jae Hee!
Hey, Eun Chong.
What are you guys doing here?
It's a bird.
It came flying from over there.
Did it?
How adorable.
How about I name the bird?
Sure!
How about "Eobeong"?
I like Eobeong.
- It's cute. - Is it?
Hi, Eobeong.
Eobeong.
I like Eobeong. It's cute.
Get your eggs.
Large eggs straight from the farm.
Get your eggs. Your eggs!
There was a monster who couldn't be saved.
But the Almighty granted him emotions.
The Almighty heard your prayers.
You're no longer...
a monster.
And in the end,
he died in extreme pain and misery as he repented for his sins.
(RIP Jung Ba Reum)
Did the deity...
do that to punish him...
or to save him?
(RIP Jung Ba Reum)
(Mouse)
(We thank Kim Yo Han and Pyo Chang Won...)
(for their special appearance.)
(Thank you for watching Mouse.)